我们需要谈谈
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
这是所有的O.M.O乐队的内容了
Here's all the orange magic orchestra ones.
O.M.O致敬日本二十世纪80年代的Yellow Magic Orchestra(Y.M.O)乐队，在日本开创了Techno类型。专辑应该为Naughty Boys
太好了，将他们放到“出色的太空摇滚”类里
Great, put them in the transcendental space rock pile.
QUADRINOMETRY-THE SECRET OF THE WAVE LIES IN CREATION
曾出现于S01E02的车库中和S01E26的车载音乐
在我家，就只有古典乐
At home, we only have classical music
和电影原声
and movie soundtracks.
我从没听过这些中的任何一种
I've never heard any of these.
The Philosophy Majors- Nietzsche's Breakdown封面致敬No Doubt乐队的Tragic Kingdom。No Doubt乐队活跃于2000年左右，主打摇滚乐。The Philosophy Majors的名字致敬加拿大的The Philosopher Kings乐队
你从没听过The Philosophy Maors的歌？
You've never heard the philosophy majors?
我的天。给我一下
Oh, man. Give it here.
今天给你开开眼
This will really knock your socks off.Come on.
Whoa!
Aah! Aah!
你们俩能融合？！
You two can fuse?!
呃...是的？
Uh...Yes?
呃，呃，呃，那真是叼-碉堡了！
Uh, uh, uh, that's in-- incredible!
从什么时候？等等，这怎么可能？
Since when? Wait, how is this even possible?
宝石人们认为是由于我是半人
The gems think it's 'cause I'm half-human.
求求你后不要告诉我家长，宇宙先生！
Please don't tell my parents, Mr. Universe.
他们不知道我一直在和史蒂文与魔法打交道
They don't know I've been doing magic stuff with Steven.
我不能告诉他们。他们理解不了-我-
I can't tell them. They're not going to understand -- I --
whoa, whoa, it -- it's okay.
我或许是地球上唯一的一个人
I may be the only human being on the planet
能理解这些
who's gonna understand.
你-你是指？
W-what do you mean?
对，你是指什么？
Yeah, what do you mean?
呃...
Well...
故事！
Story!
来吧
Come on.
我们已经准备好了
We're ready.
我没想到会这么早就告诉你
I didn't think I'd be telling you this so soon.
电视机上的海报致敬Animal Crossing（动物之森）中的K.K Slider（一只写音乐的狗）
也许最好先从这里开始
Probably best to start with this.
都准备好了吗？
Everybody ready?
1, 2, 3, 4...
我能做什么，为你？
♪ What can I do for you?
我能做什么
♪ What can I do that
是别人做不了的？
♪ no one else can do?
我能做什么，为你？
♪ What can I do for you?
人类男子啊
♪ Human man
你如此有趣
♪ you are so much fun
我从未料到，你如此赏心悦目
♪ I hadn't planned on finding you quite this entertaining ♪
我喜欢你的乐队
♪ I like your band
whoo!
而且我喜欢你的歌
♪ And I like your song
我喜欢这种，人类嬉笑的方式
♪ I like the way human beings play ♪
我喜欢参与其中
♪ I like playing along
♪ oh, oh, oh, oh, whoa-ho ♪
我能做什么，为你？
♪ what can I do for you?
我能做什么
♪ What can I do that
是别人做不了的？
♪ no one else can do?
我能做什么，为你？
♪ What can I do for you?
咦～
Tsk.
我不敢相信我录到了那个！
I can't believe I got that on video!
地球上有这玩意？
What on earth was that?!
那是彩虹石英啊
That was rainbow Quartz.
珍珠觉得融合体
Pearl thought a fusion
能给你的视频加点料
might give your video a little something extra.
这很酷，对吧？
Pretty cool, right?
我得走了，但晚些时候忙吗吗？
I have to go, but are you doing anything later?
你知道我没事
You know I'm not.
你真可爱，宇宙先生
You're adorable, Mr. Universe.
一会见
See you later.
拜拜
Bye.
嘿，我打鼓了，赶紧付钱
Hey, I hit the drums, so pay up.
这个给你
Here you go.
你只是个过客。你知道吧？——不
You're just a phase. You know that, right? No.
我实际上不知道，珍珠
I actually don't know that, Pearl.
哈，当然你不知道
Well, of course you don't.
你一点也不了解玫瑰
You don't know anything about Rose.
我知道那超喜欢我
I know she's super into me.
听着，宇宙先生
Listen Mr. Universe.
玫瑰也许觉得你很有魅力
Rose may find you charming,
但这只是因为你是个人类
but that's only because you're human.
你最多只是新奇而已
You're a novelty at best.
你怎么这么确定？
What makes you so sure?
哦，很明显。
Oh it's very simple.
人类不能融合
Humans can't fuse.
融合是宝石人之间最终极的联系
Fusion is the ultimate connection between gems.
而你不是宝石人
And you are not a gem.
那么，就没有任何人类尝试过与宝石人融合吗？
Well, has any human ever tried fusing with a gem?
呃，没有，我-我不觉得会有
Uh, no, I-I don't think so.
好，那么，我会！
Well, then, i will try!
哦，天哪，我在干嘛？
Aw, geez, what am I doing?
这些东西很贵的
These things are expensive.
天哪！她是怎么把腿抬成那样的？
Oh, geez! How did she get her legs to do that?
嘿。你挂了吗？
Hey. Are you dead?
蛤？哦，不，不。我还活着
What? Oh, no no. I'm alive.
喔，酷！
Whoa, cool!
这是刚才的我们
Aah. It's us from before.
对，我正试着
Yeah, I was just trying to
用脑子搞清楚融合舞呢
get my head around this fusion dance.
融合舞和脑子没关系！
A fusion dance ain't about your head!
等等，你们是宝石人
Wait, you guys are gems.
你们一定要帮帮我啊
You've got to help me out here.
我想要和罗丝融合
I need to be able to fuse with Rose.
首先，你需要有一个宝石作为存在的基础
First, you need the gem at the core of your being.
然后，你需要一个能变成光的身体
Then you need the body that could turn into light.
之后，你需要一个你能信任的变成光的同伴
Then you need the partner who you trust with that light.
这是比喻？
Metaphorically?
并不
Literally.
嘘。别啊，我还想看他试试
Shh. Come on. I still want to see him try.
呃，珍珠是对的。我完全做不到
Ugh, so it's true. I really can't do it.
我简直在跟自己开玩笑
I'm kidding myself with this.
我永远也不可能变成宝石人
I'm never gonna be a gem.
紫晶，给我们点私密空间
Amethyst, give us some privacy!
好！
Yeah!
我告诉你点秘密，宇宙先生
Let me tell you something, Mr. Universe.
我觉得你能做到
I think you can do it.
但像珍珠那样跳舞并没有用
But it won't work if you dance like Pearl.
你要跳出自己的风格
You have to dance like you.
你要有自己的融合的方式
You have to fuse your way.
做到开放、坦诚
Get open. Get honest.
坚持自我。这就是融合
Invent yourselves together. That's fusion.
眼...猜我了解了。
Eye... Think I get it.
此处舞蹈与布景致敬少女革命：绝对命运默示录
我们-我们没融合
We -- we didn't fuse.
啊？！
What?!
你肯定不能融合
You can't fuse.
你是人类
You're a human.
我知道！这就是问题！
I know! That's the problem!
我只是个人类
I'm just a human.
这不是问题。我爱人类
That's not a problem. I love humans.
你们都那么有趣
You're all so funny.
啊
Ugh.
听着，过去几个月非常美好——哦，是的
Look, these last few months have been great. Oh, yes.
但我开始对将来有些担心
But I'm getting a little worried about the future.
哦，那问问石榴
Oh, just ask Garnet.
我开始怀疑你是否...在乎我？
I'm starting to wonder if you...Respect me?
哦，你真幽默，宇宙先生
Oh, you're hilarious, Mr. Universe.
罗丝，求求你
Rose, please.
你能不能
Can you just...
和我说人话，哪怕是一秒？
Talk to me for one second like a real person?!
我...不是人类
I'm nota real person.
我以为-我们难道还没-
I thought -- haven't we --
难道不该这样吗？
is this not how it works?
噢
Oh.
哦，天哪
Oh, boy.
这太诡异了。你真是个外星人
This is so weird. You really are an alien.
你为什么笑了？
Why are you laughing?
你怎么又哭了？
Why are you crying?
我们该怎么办？
How are we gonna make this work?
融合？
Fusion?
不，是我们的关系
No, us.
我们真的，非常不同
We're really, really different.
我们现在该怎么办？
What do we do now?
我们先...聊聊吧
Let's just...Talk.
我根本不了解你
I barely know you.
这是个好事
That's a good thing.
我们的关系进展的真有点快了
We really rushed into this.
地球上的一切对我来讲都太快了
Everything on earth seems fast to me.
你想念你的母星吗？
Do you miss your home planet?
不，从不
No. Never.
你最后是怎么和，呃，，走到一起的？
How did you end up with, uh, Harpo, Groucho, and chico?
Harpo,Groucho和Chico是Marx Brothers（马克斯兄弟）的成员。Marx Brothers是美国喜剧界早期著名团体，与卓别林，劳埃德齐名，擅长无政府主义风格。
Harpo对应石榴（沉默寡言），Groucho对应紫晶（直率），
Chico（经常有夸张行为）
啊？哦，她们
Huh? Oh, them.
她们三个的故事可长了
Those are three long stories.
他们在干吗？——嘘！
What are they doing? Shh!
你喜欢过其他人类吗？
Have you loved other humans?
你呢？
Have you?
有——有
Yes. Yes.
那你，爱过，人类吗？
Have you ever been in love with a human?
我怎么知道？
How would I know?
这是一种折磨
It's torture.
格雷格
Greg.
罗丝
Rose.
这是折磨吗？
Is this torture?
最可怕的那种
The worst.
我实在对不起
I'm so sorry.
啊？不，不用
Huh? No. Don't be.
为什么？！
What?! Why not?!
噢，我太困惑了！
Me, too.
我也是
那么，呃，这不错
Well, uh, this is good.
我们总算有一个共同点了
We've got one thing in common.
Ha!Ohh!
他们还在跳舞？
Why are they still dancing?
那-那-那根本行不通啊
I-I-it didn't work.
不，他们成了。——啊？！
Yes, it did. What?!
已经成功了
It worked.
我觉得这是我最喜欢的人类
I think this one's my favorite.
我觉得他也是她最喜欢的人了
I think he's her favorite, too.
喔
Whoa.
那么，你们一直都不能融合？
So, you guys were never able to fuse?
呃，不能
Uh, no.
但那不如与对方沟通重要
But that wasn't as important as talking to each other.
听着，人类和宝石人——
Look, humans and gems --
这仍是一个未知的领域
it's still some pretty new territory.
你们需要共同探索
You're gonna have to work it out together.
而且，康妮，如果你需要
And, Connie, if you ever need to talk
向另一个人类谈论此事
to another human being about this,
你永远可以找我
you can always talk to me.
嗯
Mm.
人类一族？
Human beings?
人类一族
Human beings.
如果我可以做到
♪ If I could begin to be
你对我期望的一半
♪ half of what you think of me
我愿意做任何事
♪ I could do about anything
我愿学会像你一样，去爱
♪ I could even learn how to love like you ♪